Joseph McDonald Collection of Plastics Patents
Joseph McDonald Collection of Plastics Patents
- Patents
  - Patents, 1979-1987 (Box 2)
    Thermoformable Polymer Blend Composition, Michael R. Grancio; David F. Stewart and John F. Cass, inventors; Sweetheart Plastics, Inc.; May 31, 1983; Patent # 4,386,188
    Apparatus for the Continuous Formation of Biaxially Oriented Thermoplastic Materials, Thomas W. Winstead, inventor; Maryland Cup Corporation; November 8, 1983; Patent # 4,413,964
    Apparatus for the Continuous Formation of Biaxially Oriented Thermoplastic Materials and Forming Articles Therefrom by Intermittent Formings Means Interfaced Therewith, Thomas W. Winstead, inventor; Maryland Cup Corporation; May 24, 1983; Patent # 4,384,836
    Apparatus for the Continuous Formation of Biaxially Oriented Thermoplastic Materials and Forming Articles Therefrom by Intermittent Forming Means Interfaced Therewith, Thomas W. Winstead, inventor; Maryland Cup Corporation; November 22, 1983; Patent # 4,416,607
    Tamper Evident Closures and Packages, Mortimer S. Thompson, inventor; Tri-Tech Systems International Inc.; December 25, 1984; Patent # 4,489,841
    Container Tamper Detection Device, Joseph A. Resnick, inventor; January 10, 1984; Patent # 4,424,911
    Receptacle Tampering Indicator and Method Therefor, Randall A. Newkirk, inventor; February 21, 1984; Patent # 4,432,462
    Tamper Resistant Security Package, Stewart A. Darling, Tadeusz Kostanecki and George Soos, inventors; DRG Inc.; July 3, 1984; Patent # 4,457,430
    Tamper Evident Container and Method for Making the Same, Peter K. Laucis and Robert Terry, inventors; Nordson Corporation; November 6, 1984; Patent # 4,480,749
    Container Closure Integrity System, Donald R. Wloszczyna, inventor; Denerik Creativity, Inc.; March 5, 1985; Patent # 4,502,605
    Tamper-Indicating Device and Method, Robert C. Weiner, inventor; March 19, 1985; Patent # 4,505,399
    Container Seal with Tamper Indicator, Howard J. Klein and Garbor L. Szekeres, inventors; April 16, 1985; Patent # 4,511,052
    Oxygen Indicator for Packaging, Daniel Perlman and Henry Linschitz, inventors; July 2, 1985; Patent # 4,526,752
    Tamper-Evident Closure Apparatus, Jeffrey Sandhaus, inventor; May 27, 1986; Patent # 4,591,062
    Pre-Expander for Expandable Polymer Beads, Ian C. Train, inventor; June 30, 1987; Patent # 4,676,739
    Refrigerant Cooled Plastic Molding, Method and Apparatus, Robert C. Ritchie, Henry J. McKone and Richard Stamm, inventors; Dart Industries, Inc.; September 1, 1987; Patent # 4,690,789
    Method of Producing a Skin-Covered Foamed Thermoplastic, Thomas W. Winstead, inventor; June 13, 1972; Patent # 3,670,059
  - Winstead patents, 1977; 1989 (Box 2)
    Special Report; Winstead Patents: Continuous Thermoforming and Thermoplastic Foams; Michael Gigliotti & Associates; March 23, 1989
- Publications
  - Articles and papers, 1946; 1959 (Box 2)
    Electrical Insulating Materials…A Symposium: Plastic compositions for dielectric applications, W.C. Goggin and R.F. Boyer, authors; The Dow Electrical Company; Reprinted from Industrial and Engineering Chemistry, Vol. 38, Page 1090, November, 1946.
    Ethyl Cellulose Proves Self on Difficult Applications; Philip A. Belk, author; Hercules Powder Co.
    Poly-Fibre-a new approach to molding; W.C. Goggin and R.R. Bradshaw, author
    Styrene Plastics, Henno Keskkula, Alan E. Platt and Raymond F. Boyer, authors; The Dow Chemical Company; Reprinted from Kirk-Othmer: Encyclopedia of Chemical Technology, Volume 19, 2nd Edition
    Technical Papers, Plastics in Packaging, Lewis A. Bernhard, editor; Society of Plastics Engineers, Inc.; Regional Technical Conference; November 19, 1959
  - Reports, 1951; 1964,; 1966, (Box 2)
    Extrusion and Thermoforming Technical Data Prepared for Mr. J.N. McDonald, Sweetheart Plastics; January 19, 1966
    The Dow Chemical Company Report: The Extrusion of Polystyrene, I, Report No. PB-11; C.E. Beyer and F.E. Towsley, authors; The Dow Chemical Company; August 17, 1951; Plastics Basic Research Laboratory
    Report to Mr. J.N. McDonald Sweetheart Plastics, Inc., Analysis of Patents: Sheet Extrusion and Thermoforming Technology; From Edison Technical Services, Inc., Spring 1964